don't just take our word for it
ask your relatives
toothpastes
ask your friends
[Music]
three
your neighbors two
even strangers
find out just how many satisfied
customers i have more pieces
have more than one piece of the rock two
prudential life insurance policies
the fact is five out of every ten
policies prudential rights are for
people who already have a piece of the
rock that means more people come back to
prudential for another piece of the rock
than ever get started with most other
life insurance companies
[Applause]
three pieces of the rock
so far
i wonder if there's any left when you
think about your financial security see
a prudential agent come to a company
that people come back to
[Music]
credential insurance